<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visit Leblon! on Vida Leblon</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/</link><description>Recent content in Visit Leblon! on Vida Leblon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 exilium</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CT Boucherie</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/ctboucherie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/ctboucherie/</guid><description>The amount of good restaurants in Leblon always impresses me. One of my favorites is CT Boucherie. Yes, it’s expensive, but it’s worth it.
CT Boucherie was created by chef Claude Troisgros, one of the most renowned names in Brazilian gastronomy. He is the son of Pierre Troisgros, one of the founders of the French nouvelle cuisine, and brought to Brazil his experience and creativity in the kitchen. The mix he makes of French cuisine with Brazilian ingredients is fantastic.</description></item><item><title>Arpoador</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/arpoador/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/arpoador/</guid><description>Being on vacation in Leblon is really wonderful. I woke up early because I forgot to close the shades, went out to buy fresh bread at Zona Sul, not a person in sight. I had breakfast with cappuccino, minas cheese, bread and papaya. It would already be a wonderful day. It was still early, I decided to walk on the boardwalk, which was strangely empty for a weekday, a winter day in Rio.</description></item><item><title>Leblon's Dogs</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/cachorrosdoleblon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/cachorrosdoleblon/</guid><description>The other day I noticed that even dogs are happier in Leblon. I’ve been living in this neighborhood for a few years and I love seeing how owners walk their pets calmly through the streets. If the dog isn’t 100% well-behaved (and mine isn’t…), no one gives you a frown. On the contrary, people even stop to play and compliment your pet. I think this makes all the difference in the quality of life for dogs and their owners too.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Day</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/dianoleblon1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/dianoleblon1/</guid><description>I woke up early today and went straight to the beach, at Posto 11, which is three blocks from my apartment. The sun was shining, the sky was blue and the sand was warm. I took off all my jewelry, put the exact money for a coconut water and a beach umbrella in my bag. I put on my favorite bikini, grabbed my canga (brazilian sarong), book and sunscreen and went to enjoy the sea.</description></item><item><title>Degrau</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/degrau/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/degrau/</guid><description>One of my favorite restaurants in Rio de Janeiro is Restaurante Degrau in Leblon. This place is a classic of Carioca gastronomy, with almost 60 years of history and quality. The name comes from a step at the entrance that made many people stumble; the restaurant moved but the name stuck and now it’s part of the place’s charm. By the way, next door is Tropeço, a more casual bar from the same owners, with a similar kitchen.</description></item><item><title>Boteco Princesa</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/princesa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/princesa/</guid><description>The Boteco Princesa, which opened recently in Leblon, is the new bet of chef Pedro de Artagão, one of the most renowned names in Rio’s gastronomy. Boteco Princesa is a charming and laid-back place, with a decoration that mixes Portuguese and Carioca elements, and a menu that brings classic Brazilian cuisine dishes with a special touch.
The atmosphere is extremely lively, the service very friendly, the food fantastic and the price very fair.</description></item><item><title>Peixoto Sushi</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/peixoto/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/peixoto/</guid><description>Today I want to share with you an incredible gastronomic experience that I had at Peixoto Sushi, a Japanese restaurant that recently opened in Leblon, one of the most charming neighborhoods in Rio de Janeiro. Peixoto Sushi is an extension of Peixoto Deli, a famous fish market in Bairro Peixoto, in Copacabana, which offers fresh and high-quality fish. The couple Beni and Viviane Schvartz, owners of the fish market and the restaurant, are passionate about oriental cuisine and fishing, and decided to fulfill their dream of having their own sushi bar.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/about/</guid><description>Our family has lived in Leblon for more than 3 generations. They came here for the fresh air, sun and proximity with the beach, and ended up building a community. We’ve lived in San Francisco for many years, but left our heart in Leblon. Several times per year, we come to Leblon for the exact same reason our grandparents came. For us, it’s the best place in the world. We hope it becomes that for you too!</description></item><item><title>Mirante</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/mirante/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/mirante/</guid><description>An amazing place to visit in Rio de Janeiro is the Mirante do Leblon (Leblon Lookout). This is a tourist spot that offers a fantastic view of Leblon and Ipanema beaches, as well as Pedra do Arpoador and is right under the Morro Dois Irmãos. It’s a perfect place to take photos, enjoy the sunset and feel the sea breeze.
The Mirante is located at the end of Leblon beach, at the beginning of Avenida Niemeyer, on top of the rocks.</description></item><item><title>Vida Leblon Humberto</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/place/humberto/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/place/humberto/</guid><description>About this space Upscale, brand new condo in the heart of Leblon. Fully equipped kitchen with dishwasher and washer/dryer, a cute balcony, and steps from the beach, the subway and the best restaurants and shopping in Rio. Every room has AC, ceiling fan and TV.
Living room with open kitchen, bar seating couch and 50&amp;quot; TV, with cute balcony and hammock. Kitchen with dishwasher, washer/dryer, small laundry space, and full size refrigerator.</description></item></channel></rss>