<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>things to do on Vida Leblon</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/tags/things-to-do/</link><description>Recent content in things to do on Vida Leblon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 exilium</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/tags/things-to-do/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arpoador</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/arpoador/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/arpoador/</guid><description>Being on vacation in Leblon is really wonderful. I woke up early because I forgot to close the shades, went out to buy fresh bread at Zona Sul, not a person in sight. I had breakfast with cappuccino, minas cheese, bread and papaya. It would already be a wonderful day. It was still early, I decided to walk on the boardwalk, which was strangely empty for a weekday, a winter day in Rio.</description></item><item><title>Leblon's Dogs</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/cachorrosdoleblon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/cachorrosdoleblon/</guid><description>The other day I noticed that even dogs are happier in Leblon. I’ve been living in this neighborhood for a few years and I love seeing how owners walk their pets calmly through the streets. If the dog isn’t 100% well-behaved (and mine isn’t…), no one gives you a frown. On the contrary, people even stop to play and compliment your pet. I think this makes all the difference in the quality of life for dogs and their owners too.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Day</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/dianoleblon1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/dianoleblon1/</guid><description>I woke up early today and went straight to the beach, at Posto 11, which is three blocks from my apartment. The sun was shining, the sky was blue and the sand was warm. I took off all my jewelry, put the exact money for a coconut water and a beach umbrella in my bag. I put on my favorite bikini, grabbed my canga (brazilian sarong), book and sunscreen and went to enjoy the sea.</description></item><item><title>Mirante</title><link>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/mirante/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.vidaleblon.com/en/post/mirante/</guid><description>An amazing place to visit in Rio de Janeiro is the Mirante do Leblon (Leblon Lookout). This is a tourist spot that offers a fantastic view of Leblon and Ipanema beaches, as well as Pedra do Arpoador and is right under the Morro Dois Irmãos. It’s a perfect place to take photos, enjoy the sunset and feel the sea breeze.
The Mirante is located at the end of Leblon beach, at the beginning of Avenida Niemeyer, on top of the rocks.</description></item></channel></rss>